《终空》前情提要
Previously on "Final Space"...
经过五年孤身一人的飞船牢狱生活
After five years of jail time alone on a prison ship,
我们的英雄盖瑞  交到了不止一个  而是两个朋友
our hero Gary made not one, but two friends.
其中一个是行星杀手  另一个是致命赏金猎人
One is a planet-killer, the other a deadly bounty hunter.
两人都和总司令有着密切关系
And both of them lead right back to the Lord Commander,
至于总司令  他是一个混蛋
who's kind of a jerk-face. Well, guess what?!
故事就要开始了  所以坐稳扶好吧
We're off to a great start, so buckle up those butt cheeks,
因为接下来的故事可是非常精彩呢
'cause things are about to get heavy.
盖瑞  你还有8分钟氧气可用
Gary, you have eight minutes of oxygen left.
HUE  如果你还能再活8分钟
H.U.E., if you had eight minutes to live
而且可以为所欲为的话  你会做什么？
and you could do anything you wanted, what would you do?
正在计算  啊
Facticulating. Ahh.
我会把我的人工智能移植到一具骨肉之躯里
I would transfer my A.I. into a corporeal being
然后去看看巴黎
and go see Paris.
哦  这也太无聊了吧！我的意思是  不  这其实挺酷的...
Oh, that's lame! I mean, wow. Super... cool.
你会做什么  盖瑞？
What would you do, Gary?
我想做所有的事  我想和奎恩一起做所有的事
Absolutely anything. And I mean anything with Quinn.
甚至一起看《太空驾驶》我都不介意
I mean, we could watch "Space Drive" for all I care.
很抱歉  事情到了现在的地步
I'm sorry things turned out this way.
坏事总会发生的
Crap happens.
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Two
终空  第一季第二集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
拉克斯星团
432G区
洞  洞  洞  洞  盖洞洞
♪ Holes, holes, holes, holes, cover up these holes ♪
塞洞洞
♪ Plug these holes ♪
洞  洞  洞  洞
♪ Holes, holes, holes, holes ♪
到处都是洞  到处都是洞
♪ Nothing but holes, nothing but holes ♪
♪ Nothing but holes, but holes, but holes ♪
洞  洞  洞  洞  盖洞洞
♪ Holes, holes, holes, holes, cover up these holes ♪
塞洞洞  洞洞  洞洞
♪ Plug these holes, holes, holes ♪
到处都是洞
♪ Nothing but holes ♪
洞  洞  洞
♪ Holes, holes, holes ♪
都是洞
♪ But holes ♪
塞... 塞
♪ Plug these ... plug ♪
塞洞洞  洞洞
♪ Plug these holes, holes ♪
洞  洞  洞  洞
♪ Holes, holes, holes, holes ♪
奎恩  是我  盖瑞  我这边目前非常不错
Quinn, it's me, Gary. Things have been great on my end.
我交了一个在我看来是潜在的新朋友
I made what I believe to be a potential new friend.
是的  他登船本来是想杀了我
Yes, he boarded the ship to kill me
顺便把我的小绿球朋友绑走的
and take my little green ball friend,
不过阿瓦卡多打得一手好牌
but Avocato is one great card player.
要是再打牌  我就一枪崩了自己
Any more cards and I will shoot myself.
你要是不打  我就一枪崩了你
I'm gonna shoot you if you don't play cards.
- 那你就崩了我吧   - 呃  哦... 真的...
- I'll let you shoot me. - Um, oh ... real...
- 算了  那我就崩了自己好了！   - 什... 什么？为啥？
- Well, then I'm gonna shoot myself! - W-What? Why?
你他喵的猜去吧  随便你猜
Frickin' figure it out. Figure it out.
我们的新成员是这个小家伙！
And our newest member is this little guy!
他叫月饼
His name's Mooncake.
Ooh!
人人都喜欢他
Everyone loves him.
这个小绿鼻涕虫是个能毁灭行星的超级武器
That little green snot-ball is a planet-destroying super-weapon
他能把我们都杀死
that's gonna get us killed.
这位先生  你过分了
You, sir, just stepped over the line.
月饼也是有情感的
Mooncake has feelings.
你刚刚的话  就像用猫尿浇了它一身
And you just peed all over them with your cat whiz.
嗯  我这边目前还不错
Yep. Things have been going pretty great.
有空回我一下  不急
Get back to me. No rush.
只是  我可能已经有差不多五年
It's just I haven't talked to a human lady person
没和人类女性说过话了
in, like, five years.
好的  发送自你永远的  闪电侠盗
Well, yours forever. Thunder bandit!
已发送  我成功了... 又一次！
Message sent. I crushed it... again!
地球
我是奎恩
Quinn.
你好啊奎恩  我是三烦
Hey, Quinn, it's Tribor.
一架无疆守卫的飞船坠毁了
An Infinity Guard ship has crashed.
至于它为什么会坠毁？我们不知道  我们需要你来现场
How did it crash, we don't know. We need you on the scene.
我马上就来
On my way.
哈  哦  妈耶  哦  老天  哦！
Ha. Oh, mama. Oh, boy. Oh!
监测到非法扫描
Unauthorized scan detected.
你在干啥  盖瑞？
What's ya doing, Gary?
找到你了  总司令... 啊！
Gotcha. Lord Commander ... agh!
嗯  设置去泰拉·康·普莱姆的航线
Hmm. Set course for Tera Con Prime.
这他妈的是啥？
What the heck is this thing?
- 一个文特克西秘密探测器... 是特克的   - 当然了  “特克”
- A Ventrexian stealth probe ... Turk. - Of course, "Turk."
“特克”又他妈是谁？
Who the hell is Turk?
一个赏金猎人... 就像我一样  如果他扫描到了月饼
A bounty hunter ... like me. If he scanned Mooncake,
他就会立刻回去  向总司令复命
he'll be on his way back to the Lord Commander
- 顺便搬来救兵   - 嗯
- to gather reinforcements. - Mm-hmm.
- 除非我们先把他截下来   - 嗯
- Unless we stop him first. - Mm-hmm.
如果我们不行动  他们就会把月饼抓走的
If we don't, they will capture Mooncake.
- 呃   - 然后把我们带到暗区
- Unh-nh. - And take us to the Dark Zone.
- 呃   - 然后用泽尔贡鼻涕虫折磨我们
- Unh-nh.  - And torture us with zargon slugs.
- 呃   - 我们会陷入永恒的
- Unh-nh. - Or we're gonna suffer pain
- 苦恼和伤痛   - 哦
- and anguish for eternity. - Oh.
然而能阻止他的唯一办法  只有用盐
And the only way to stop them is with salt.
- 哦   - 而且暗区里
- Oh. - And there's no salt
- 是没有盐的   - 嗯
- in the Dark Zone. - Hmm.
看起来真的是束手无策了啊
Sounds like I got these buttery buns into a hot vise.
- 我要怎么让他们停下？   - 你做不到的
- How do I stop them? - You don't.
不过如果咱俩一起的话  可以试一试
But together, we've got a shot.
把我从手铐里放出来  然后我们去追他
Get me out of these cuffs, and we'll go after him.
哇哇哇哇哇  牛仔！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, cowboy!
你才想杀我来着！
You tried to kill me!
如果你想让我相信你  我们得握个手
If you want me to trust you, first we clasp.
- 我才不握   - 你非握不可  你一定得和我握手
- I'm not doing that. - Oh, yes, you will. You will do that.
刚刚我们还一起愉快地打了牌
We've enjoyed recreational cards together.
这就是下一步  一个手与手相连的纽带
This is the next step. A hand-to-hand bond that forges
铸就一座崭新的信任丰碑
the completion of a newfound trust.
我们不至于脱到全裸来展示坦诚吧？
We don't have to get balls to the wind naked, do we?
按理来说是需要的  不过你很幸运
Tradition demands yes. But you're lucky.
我是革新的进步主义者
I'm more of a progressive.
启动信任模式
Trust mode engaged.
五年来  我终于要第一次下船了！
It's been five years since I've been off this ship!
我已经对冒险蠢蠢欲动了！让我们把他截下来吧！
I am pumped for adventure! Let's get this guy!
HUE  打开气锁
H.U.E., open the airlock.
你是个囚犯
You are a prisoner.
我怎么知道你会不会逃跑？
How will I know you won't run?
- 我没处可...   - 已注射
- I got nowhere to g... - Inject.
哦！这他妈是啥？！
Ow! What the freak was that?!
如果五个小时后你还没返回飞船
If you are not back aboard this ship in five hours,
你的大脑会抽搐痉挛  然后爆掉
your brain will go into convulsive spasms and then explode.
- 咱们走！   - 不带上月饼吗？
- Let's go! - Shouldn't we take Mooncake?
太危险了  快点  快点！
It's too dangerous. Make haste, make haste!
我会想你的  小家伙  好好的
I'll miss you, bud. Be good.
别在我的东西上拉屎撒尿
And don't whiz on any of my stuff.
泰拉·康·普莱姆
18650区
哦  哦！街边烤肉！
Oh, oh! Street meat!
他们有街边烤肉  阿瓦卡多！
They got street meat, Avocato!
- 集中注意力   - 呃  我在集中
- Focus. - Okay, I'm focused.
好的  我们去找特克
All right, we're getting Turk.
为了银河  为了永恒  为了总司令
For the galaxy, for eternity, for Lord Commander.
咱们竟然能到这一步  你该感到幸运
You're lucky that we even made it here.
他们对智人很不友好的
They don't take kindly to Homo Sapiens.
现在去24区  弄你的身份证件
Now let's go to Tier 24 and get you identification papers.
- 我不需要证件   - 否则他们会把你液化的
- I don't need papers. - Or they'll liquify you.
你刚说的是“液化”吗？还是我脑子痉挛听错了？
Did you just say liquify? Or was that a brain spasm?
这... 这可能吗？哦我的天哪  可能
I-Is it happening? Oh, my crap, it's happening.
否则我们会杀了你的
Or we'll kill you.
盖瑞  别走太远
Gary, stay close.
好的  别担心  我哪也不去
Right, don't worry. I'm not going anywhere.
- 盖瑞！   - 买点烤肉！
- Gary! - Getting some street meat!
请出示证件！
Identification papers!
呃  我一定是把它落在  呃...
Um, I must have left them in, um...
有人逃跑了
We got a runner.
- 或许我们真的得搞个证件   - 嗯
- Maybe we should get some papers. - Mm-hmm.
欢迎来到飞机库！
Welcome to the hangar bay!
不过我更喜欢称之为“虎穴”  我猜你很奇怪为什么要这样
But I call it the tiger's nest. And I bet you're wondering why.
别急  我会告诉你的
Well, okay, I'll tell you.
Whoo!
呃  抱歉  你需要帮助吗？
Uh, excuse me, can I help you?
呃  你好  快跑！快跑！
Uh, hello. Run away! Run away!
啊  阿瓦卡多  很高兴见到你
Ahh. Avocato, it's so good to see you.
是哪阵风把你刮来敝处的？
What brings you to my little shop of doo-dads?
别说废话  克拉伦斯
Cut the crap, Clarence!
没错  别说废话  克拉伦斯
Yeah, cut the crap, Clarence.
- 我们需要证件   - 是的  证件
- We need papers. - That's right, papers.
证件可不便宜
Well, papers are not cheap.
- 哦！   - 你的命也不便宜  我可救过你一命
- Oh! - Neither is your life, and I saved that.
是的  没错  你确实救过我
Yes, right, I suppose you did.
但这真是最后一次了  你的证件好说
But this is the last time. Your papers are easy.
- 但这个灵长动物...   - 嘿！
- But this primate... - Hey!
...他的证件可不好办
... is gonna be much more difficult.
- 把你的手指头从我肚皮上拿走   - 哦！它会说话
- Get your finger out of my tummy. - Ooh! It speaks.
我猜你可以训练各种东西说话
I guess you can train anything.
我想什么时候戳你就什么时候戳你  你个灵长动物！
I'll touch you any time I wish, primate!
哼
Hmph.
好的  不对  不是这个  等一下
Yes, no, not that one. Hold on a second.
下面那个  那个应该可以  好的  就是它了
Down here at the bottom, possibly. Oh, yes, here we go.
- 一个霍布拉怪的尸皮   - 我得钻进这里面？
- Skin of a dead Hooblat. - I have to get in this thing?
这像个油腻腻的馅饼皮一样
It's like a slippery pita pocket.
你想被液化吗？
You want to be liquefied and have Mooncake
想让月饼和银河一号毁灭吗？
and the Galaxy 1 destroyed?
不... 你他喵是怎么知道的？
No, h... how the hell do you know that?
到处都在传  人人都在说这个
It's everywhere. It's all anyone's talking about.
哈
Huh.
快钻进去！
Get in the skin!
为了月饼
For Mooncake.
哦我的天哪  好暖和！
Oh, my God, it's so warm!
哦  而且...好湿！哦
Oh, it's ... and wet! Oh.
其实感觉还挺不错的
It actually kind of feels kind of nice,
就像一双暖洋洋又潮乎乎的居家拖鞋
like a pair of warm, wet house slippers.
这根本没道理
It doesn't make any sense.
我知道  根本没道理
I know. It doesn't make any sense.
我多希望这有道理啊  一切“道理”都去了哪里啊？
I wish there was sense. Where did all the sense go?
我不明白  这可是帝国T3机型
I don't get it. It's an Imperium T3.
- 这种机型不会坠毁的   - 不会坠毁的  你说的对
- These things don't crash. - They don't crash, you're right.
根本没道理  为啥会坠毁呢？
It doesn't make any sense. Why would it crash?
三烦  看着我的眼睛
Tribor, look me in the eye.
- 请你闭嘴   - 我的确应该闭嘴
- Now shut up. - I should shut up.
- 为什么我还在讲话呢？   - 你看见这个了吗？
- Why do I keep talking? - Are you reading this?
引力常数在波动
The gravitational constant is shifting.
- 我看到了  我确实看到了！   - 如此强劲的干扰
- I am seeing it. I am! - A disturbance this strong
足以撕裂宇宙
can literally tear the universe apart.
入侵警告
Intruder alert.
启动反重力方案
Initiating anti-gravity countermeasures.
机器人  启动防御措施
SAMES, initiate defense sequence.
话说回来  我好像还是个安全负责人还是啥的
Anyway, I'm kind of in charge of security around here,
于是我需要你帮个大忙
which brings me to a big ask.
你能过去帮我拿块饼干吗？
Could you go out there and get me a cookie?
Chookity.
成功！
Score!
我就坐在这里  守卫堡垒
All right, I'll stay here and guard the fort.
我看起来怎么样？说真的
How do I look? Be honest.
- 也就2分吧   - 只有2分？
- I'd give you a 2. - Just a 2?
我得弄个头发啥的
Get my hair done or something, you know.
- 别弄好吗？   - 不  我很严肃的  我可以染个高亮
- How about no? - No, seriously, I could get highlights.
- 或者染个渐变色的头发   - 我简直不敢相信你
- I could get ombre hair, you know? - I can't believe it.
要相信我  因为我马上就要染渐变色了
Believe it, because this ombre hair is happening.
- 不  特克！   - 哦我的天哪  是特克
- No. Turk! - Oh, crap, it is Turk.
你瞅啥？你瞅啥？
What are you looking at? What are you looking at?
- 咱们走   - 走
- Let's go. - Let's go.
嗯
Hmm.
你以为你能临阵脱逃的吧？
Thought you could rat us out, huh?
你个老东西又是啥？
How the hell are you, you old bag?
成吧  这话真伤人
Okay. That just hurts.
阿瓦卡多！
Avocato!
- 不！   - 给我个合理的解释
- No! - Give me one reason
为什么你把我扔在那艘飞船上等死  不然我马上杀了你
I don't kill you right now for leaving me to die on that ship!
因为我知道你儿子在哪
Because I know where your son is.
我儿子？在哪？他在哪？
My son? Where? Where is he?
- 43号牢房   - 他... 他真的在那？
- Holding cell 43. - He's... he's here?
- 快放我走   - 我会放你的
- Now let me go. - I'll let you go.
我要把你放进地狱里
I'll let you go to Hell.
我来了  小卡多
I'm coming, Little Cato.
玛莲妮·都文特  4层
Melanie Dewinter, level 4.
玛莲妮·都... 啥... 啥？！
Melanie Du... what ... what?!
啊！哦！
Aah! Oh!
- 妈咪！   - 妈咪！
- Mommy! - Mommy!
- 你回来了！   - 我回来了！
- You're back! - I sure am!
- 哦不！   - 玛莲妮！
- Oh, no! - Melanie!
哦  他们还说你死了呢！
Oh, they told us you were dead!
哦！我和你妹妹不该续弦的
Oh! Everything with your sister was a mistake.
我的天哪
Oh, my crap.
坐好
Sit tight.
我听不见你
I can't hear you.
我搞砸了  我都搞砸了
I messed up. I messed up bad!
我不会把你丢在这的  我答应你
But I'm not gonna leave you here. I promise.
我会用尽全力救你
I'll do whatever it takes.
不  爸！爸  跑啊！这是个陷阱！
No, Dad! Dad, run! It's a trap!
爸  小心啊！
Dad, watch out!
爸  爸  爸  不！
Dad, Dad, Dad, no!
把他带到总司令那
Take him to the Lord Commander.
我最爱妈咪了！
I love Mommy more!
不  明明我更爱妈咪！
No, I love Mommy more!
好了  好了... 停...
Okay, just, uh ... stop ...
别再扯我了  小家伙们
keep ... stop tugging too hard, babies.
玛莲妮！哦天哪！
Melanie?! Oh, God!
你们现在说不定有些问题想问我
So you probably have a few questions.
滚出去  你个疯子！
Get out of here, you maniac!
呀！
Hyah!
哈！
Huh!
阿瓦卡多！
Avocato!
朋友间的握手
The clasp of friends.
再过两个小时  我的脑子就要从眼眶里炸出去了
Only two hours till my brain shoots out of my eyes.
我得快点
I gotta move fast.
地球
长官  有紧急情况
Sir, there's an emergency.
我们得让无疆守卫的所有巡飞舰立即着陆
We need to ground all Infinity Guard cruisers immediately.
什么？！又来了  奎恩
What?! Not again, Quinn.
有个宇宙灾难正在发生
There's a cosmic disaster taking place.
- 我们得查清楚是什么引...   - 奎恩  闭嘴吧
- We need to find out what's causing ... - Quinn, shut up!
那架帝国T3坠毁是人为因素造成的
The Imperium T3 crashed because of human error.
是吗？你讲点科学吧  你个傻子
Yeah? Tell that to science. You're an idiot.
- 支持一下我  舰长   - 你该走了  奎恩
- Back me up, Captain. - Time to leave, Quinn.
成吧  舰长也是个傻子
Okay. The Captain is also an idiot.
中尉？
Lieutenant?
你们都是傻子！傻子  傻子！
You're all idiots! Idiots, idiots!
你们都是傻子吗？为什么你们是傻子？
Are you idiots? Why would you all be idiots?
我还以为你们很聪明来着
I think you're all very smart.
好吧  我是该走了
Well, I gotta go.
请停下！停下  不然我不得不
Stop! Stop, or I will be forced to...
手动重载人工智能了  HUE已下线
Manual override of A.I. H.U.E. disabled...
阿瓦卡多  我们有约在先
Avocato. We had a deal.
你答应我会抓来E-351的
You promised me E-351
然而你失败了... 又一次失败了
and you failed... again.
相信我  我能做到的  我已经很接近了
Trust me, I can do this. I'm close.
哦！哦  那你可得快点了  它什么时候才能回到我手上？
Ooh! Ooh, hurray. When will it be mine?
等等  你是偷偷把它带来了吗？这是游戏吗？
Wait, are you hiding it on you? Is this a game?
- 我喜欢玩游戏   - 我没带来它
- I love games. - I don't have it.
不过我能给您抓来那个带着他的人
But I can get you the man who does.
那个人叫盖瑞
His name is Gary.
我把他给您抓来  您把我儿子还给我
I get you him, you give me back my son.
这可不成
No deal.
你在这啊！我这一天啊  老天爷
There you are! What a day I've had, man.
我  我猜我破坏了一个家庭
I-I think I destroyed a family.
哦  那我们离开这里如何？
Oh. So how about we get out of here?
你就是“那个盖瑞”吧
You must be the Gary.
呃... 实际上  我就叫“盖瑞”
Okay... Actually, it's just Gary.
- “那个盖瑞”   - 就只有“盖瑞”
- The Gary. - Just Gary.
没有... 我的意思是... 没“那个”...
You know, just ... just ... there's no...
“那个”到底是哪来的？
Where's this "the" coming from?
呃  这个不错诶  但是... 阿瓦卡多  快跑！
Well, this has been great. But... Avocato, run!
我还没和你自我介绍呢
I haven't introduced myself.
我是总司令
I am the Lord Commander.
哦  就是你啊  好极了
Oh, is that you? That's fantastic.
但是我们确实得... 阿瓦卡多！
But we really gotta ... Avocato!
你拿了我的东西  我想把它要回来！
You have something of mine, and I want it!
过来  那个盖瑞
Come here, the Gary.
发生了啥？哦我的天哪！
What is going on? Oh, God!
我猜... 被别人惦记着是一件很酷的事
Okay, this is ... it's nice to be wanted.
但你实在是... 太惦记我了
But this is ... this is too much want.
你是给我E-351呢
Are you going to give me E-351,
还是让我把你的四肢一根根拔下来呢？
or should I tear you limb from limb?
阿瓦卡多  我需要一点帮助  哦！哦！
Avocato, a little help. Oh! Oh! [Music]
阿瓦卡多  朋友之间的握手！
Avocato, the clasp of friends!
求你了  天啦噜！阿瓦卡多！
Please, man! Avocato!
朋友模式！开启！
Friend mode! Engaged!
朋友？他才刚刚背叛了你
Friend? He was just betraying you.
你骗人  我们握过手的  对吧  伙计？
Untrue. We clasped hands. Right, bro?
我当时孤注一掷了  我想救我的儿子
I was desperate, man. I was trying to save my son.
哦  我的老天爷！
Oh, my God!
你个智障！那是老子的胳膊！
You idiot! That's my freakin' arm!
你把老子的胳膊拔下来了！啊！
You just ripped the thing off! Aah!
哦我的天哪！这都他喵的是什么鬼？
Oh, my God! Oh, what the freak?!
血都喷出来了！
I'm spraying all my blood!
我要杀到你脸都不剩！
I am going to murder your face off!
- 我要杀到你只剩下脸？   - 你在胡扯些啥啊！
- I will murder your face on? - That doesn't make any sense!
- 跑啊！快跑！   - 哦！
- Run! Come on! - Oh!
追他们！
After them!
- 哦  怎么这么多台阶！   - 别说话了  你个白痴！
- Oh, there's so many stairs! - Quit talking, you idiot!
为什么有这么多台阶？！
Why are there so many stairs?!
- 盖瑞  我不能丢下我的儿子   - 好的  那我们去救他...
- Gary, I can't leave my son. - Oh, we're going, all right ...
不过得快点... 在我脑子爆掉之前！
and fast ... before my brain explodes!
我们来不及回运输船了
We're not gonna make it back to the transporter.
看来有一艘新的飞船等着我们
Looks like we got a new ride.
好吧  这个不太理想  不过也算是艘飞船  哦老天！
Okay, not ideal, but still a ride. Oh, come on!
- 我都不知道那是啥了   - 咪咪咪咪咪咪
- I don't even know what that is. - Mi-mi-mi-mi-mi-mi.
去他喵的！
Crap it hard!
- 我们跳到栈道上   - 你疯了吗？
- We jump to the catwalk. - Are you insane?
不  我已经“超级疯”了
No, I'm super insane.
哦天哪！
Oh my God!
干得漂亮  我需要那件衣服
Attaboys. I'll need that suit back.
- 我们在往下掉啊！哦天哪！   - 什么... 啊啊啊！
- We're falling! Oh, my gosh! - What... ahhh!
哦天哪  大卫  孩子们！是我  你们的妈妈！
Oh, my God, David, kids! It's me, your mother!
不  我的胳膊！我把我胳膊落在上面了！
No, my arm! I forgot my arm back up there!
这可不妙！HUE  接线！接线啊！
This is no good! H.U.E., pick up, pick up!
- 那些是我猜的东西吗？   - 毒蛇炮塔
- Are those what I think they are? - Viper turrets.
好的  不妙啊  非常不妙啊！
Okay, that's not good. That's not good!
- 快  抱我   - 抱你？
- Quick, hug me. - Hug you?
- 抱抱你的朋友！   - 啥？！
- Hug a friend! - What?!
抱我啊！哦  我们抱起来了！
Hug me! Oh, we're hugging!
HUE？HUE  来啊！
H.U.E.? H.U.E., come in!
奎恩  奎恩  你去哪？
Quinn. Quinn, where are you going?
我要劫一架鹰式机  有大事要发生了
To the first Hawk I can jack. Something big is happening,
我可没工夫等那些指挥官们
and I'm not waiting while command sits around,
天天坐在那闲的玩蛋  我可能无法阻止这件事
twiddling their wieners. Maybe I can't stop it,
不过我一定要弄清楚这是什么  掩护我
but I'm going to find out what it is. Cover for me.
为什么他们会闲的玩蛋呢？为什么呢？
Why would they be twiddling their wieners? Why?
等等  我需要六块饼干
Wait, I'm gonna need six cookies.
再来一块吧  所以是七块... 八块饼干
And another one. So seven ... eight cookies.
算了吧  九块！
Wait, nine cookies!
我觉得我还是去帮他一把吧
I guess I better give him a hand.
KVN  总有一天  你要拯救银河一号的
KVN, you're going to have to save the Galaxy 1 someday.
在你的体内  就存着答案
Inside of you now is the answer.
嗨月饼  我叫夜幕
Hey, Mooncake. My name is Nightfall.
不要让盖瑞因你而死
Don't let Gary die because of you.
HUE！来啊  HUE！
H.U.E.! Come in, H.U.E.!
啊... 我在  盖瑞？
Arrr... yes, Gary?
什么鬼  HUE？！我联系你那么久了
What the crap, H.U.E.?! I've been calling you.
我们需要你救我们出去  越快越好！
We need you to scoop us up A.S.A.P.P.!
我来了  盖瑞
On my way, Gary.
嘿诶诶... 盖瑞  你胳膊不见了
He-e-ey... Gary, your arm is gone.
哦天哪  真的？真的吗？
Oh, my gosh. Is it? Really?
我当然知道胳膊不见了  你这坨烂屎！
I know my arm is gone, you decaying pile of fecal matter!
现在  快把我脑子里的东西弄出来  HUE
Now get this thing out of my head, H.U.E.
哦  那个其实不会爆炸的  盖瑞
Oh. It was never going to explode, Gary.
那只是我和你开个玩笑而已
That's just my sense of humor.
这五年来你就开了一个玩笑  这就是你的玩笑？！
You make one joke in five years, and that is the one you tell?!
时间观念乃是一切  盖瑞
Timing... is everything, Gary.
嗯  哦
Hmm. Whoo.
我的胳膊！我的胳膊！
My arm! My arm!
有趣  我们可以做手术给你移植一个电子手臂
Interesting. We can surgically implant an animatronic arm on you.
盖瑞  你离开的时候  有个入侵者...
Gary, while you were gone, an intruder ...
你丫闭嘴  KVN  你没听到这个吗？
Shut your face hole, KVN. Didn't you just hear the news?
我要有机器手臂了
I'm getting a robot arm.
不过需要一个人来执行手术  盖瑞
But someone will need to perform the procedure, Gary.
我来吧
I'll do it.
你？
You?
开启临时动脉分流
Create temporary arterial shunt.
我觉得我们会成为超级好的朋友的  老天哪
I thought we were gonna be like super friends, man.
过去的三年里  我只有一个任务  盖瑞
I've had one mission for the past three years, Gary,
- 那就是找到我的儿子   - 你应该早和我说的
- and that is to find my son. - You should have told me.
我们进行过朋友间的握手
We did the clasp of friends.
如果你说了  我本会真心帮你把你儿子救回来的
I would have straight-up helped you get your son back.
什么？为什么？你才刚刚认识我
What? Why? You barely know me.
老兄  咱俩一起打了九个小时牌
Yo, we played nine hours of cards together.
这对你来说可能不算什么  不过对我来说意义非凡
That might not mean something to you, but it did to me.
露出骨骼  以便电镀
Expose bone for plating.
是朋友  就要互相支持
Friends help each other through thick
无论春风和煦  无论艰难险阻
and thin and thinner and nothing.
我无以为报
I have nothing to give in return.
你有的  你回报了你的友谊
Yeah, you do, yo. Your friendship, yo.
我在这被关了这么久  目之所及全是机器人
I've been stuck here for so long with just freakin' robots.
看  机器人  机器人  机器人  机器人  机器人  机器人！
Look robot, robot, robot, robot, robot, robot!
- 全他妈是机器人   - 那是冰箱  盖瑞
- Freakin' robot. - That's the refrigerator, Gary.
真的？因为我和那东西之间
Really? Because I've had some serious,
进行过若干严肃又黑暗的对话  它了解我的一切
dark conversations with that thing. It knows everything about me.
闭上你的嘴  你个撒谎的机器人！
Keep your mouth shut, you lying robot!
微血管移植覆盖已完成
Micro-vascular transplant coverage complete.
我们的友谊确实是以一种非常规方式开始的  不过...
It's an unconventional way to start a friendship, but ...
- 嗯？   - 嘘！
- Hmm? - Shh!
不用说什么了  只要握手就好
No words. Only clasps.
- 兄弟  你这次来真的了？   - 无比真实
- Bro, you being real this time? - As real as it gets, baby.
那我也向你保证  我们会把你儿子救回来的
Then I promise you, we will get your son back.
- 并且保证月饼的安全   - 还要把那家伙杀到脸都不剩
- And keep Mooncake safe. - And murder that guy's face off.
我可不认为这是个好主意
I don't think that's a great idea.
开启真实友谊模式
Real raw friendship mode engaged
Ooh!
你马上就要去一个  你父亲永远也找不到的地方了
Where you're going, your father will never find you.
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com